<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
    <ServerGroup Name="I Am Legend" Logo="" Description="Light up the darkness">
        <Server Name="I Am Legend" Logo="">
            <Description>
I AM LEGEND

A small mod that tries to emulate the movie of the same name.

SYNOPSIS:
Six billion people on Earth when the infection hit...
The Krippin Virus had a 90 percent kill rate; that's 5.4 BILLION people, dead. Crashed and bled out. Dead. Less than one-percent immunity.
That left 12 million healthy people, like you. The other 588 MILLION turned into Dark Seekers, and then they got hungry, and they killed and fed on everybody. EVERYBODY!
Every single person that you or I has ever known is dead! DEAD!
THERE IS NO GOD!

ABOUT THE 'I AM LEGEND' MOD.
Zombies (Dark Seekers) DO NOT spawn in the wild during the day. You are free to move about the world, but be warned...
Buildings are DANGEROUS. They are filled with fast-moving enemies, and you'll need to be careful when looking for supplies.
There are no traders; all trader compounds have been abandoned.
When night falls, you'll want to be inside and well hidden. Dark Seekers will be out in force, and they're hungry ...

Changes from the vanilla game:
As stated above, no zombies spawn outside during the day.
All buildings have a minimum of "infested" levels of zombies. This can be increased via a new game options tab, to super infested, or ultra infested.
Zombies move QUICKLY, ALL THE TIME!
Come nightfall, there will be 5x the number of zombies that you would normally see in vanilla.
Feral sense is ON at night, with 50% more range than vanilla. If you want to avoid Darkseekers, you'll need to stay hidden and quiet.
There are NO TRADERS. If you generate a new world, there will be no traders spawned. If you use an existing world, all traders will be replaced with abandoned compounds.
The chance of finding a water filter for a dew collector is DRASTICALLY INCREASED from vanilla. Not guaranteed from a broken dew collector, but a high chance.
Action skills replace most tool and weapon perks. Attribute skills cost the same amount of points as vanilla, but perks cost 2 points instead of 1.
The loot probability for books and magazines is tied to the action skill for that tool or weapon. The higher your skill, the better chance of finding books or magazines for that tool or weapon.
Headlamps and nightvision goggles have been removed.
You spawn in with a backpack, which you can open to give you your starting items.

Main differences between the movie and the mod:
While Darkseekers will not SPAWN outside, they will chase you out of buildings, and follow you outside, regardless of the time of day.
Unfortunately, you don't have a pet dog	. Sorry.
You can't "capture" a zombie to look for a cure. You just play the game as you normally would.

Hope you have fun with it!

CONTRIBUTORS:

Action Skills template		JoeSloeMoe
Bloodmoon Server status		Kanaverum
No Traders mod				PULLMYLEVER
WMMGameOptions				w00kien00kie

Also thanks to Frantic_Dan and redbeardt for base xml code for HUD changes, and thanks to Khaine for basis of the action skills feature.		
            </Description>
            <Discord></Discord>
            <Donate></Donate>
            <EAC>Disabled</EAC>
            <Version>Latest</Version>
            <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
            <Downloads>
                <Download></Download>
            </Downloads>
        </Server>
    </ServerGroup>
</Servers>